blogdum.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy - BlogDum

## Privacy Policy for blogdum.com

The privacy of our visitors to [blogdum.com](http://blogdum.com/) is important to us.

At blogdum.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. We store your personal information such as email, name, etc. when you use and visit _blogdum.com_ , and how we protect your information. We never sell your any personal information to third parties.

 **Log Files:**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files(Database). The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer,Opera,Safari,Firefox or Chrome), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. This is information is only used for tracking purpose to check out website stats.

 ** **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**:**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences only when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a social or ad popup once in your visit, or the ability to register/login to some of our features.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by changing preferences in programs such as Kaspersky, Norton,etc. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

 **Disclaimer:**

All the contents in _blogdum.com_ is for educational and informational purpose only. We do not take any responsibility for any loss caused to you by the information on _blogdum.com_.

[Contact us](http://blogdum.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us") for any information related your queries.

### Share and Enjoy
